<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ATM Madat</string>
    <string name="lang_selection">Choose your language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="Marathi">मराठी</string>
    <string name="hindi">हिंदी</string>
    <string name="punjabi">ਪੰਜਾਬੀ</string>
    <string name="malayalam">മലയാളം</string>
    <string name="gujarati">ગુજરાતી</string>
    <string name="Telugu">తెలుగు</string>
    <string name="Kannada">ಕನ್ನಡ</string>
    <string name="msg">Welcome All</string>
    <string name="nxt">Next</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="choose_your_bank">Choose Your Bank</string>
    <string name="back">previous</string>
    <string name="option_selc">Choose Your Option</string>
    <string name="bank_information">Bank information</string>
    <string name="atm_card_information">Atm card information</string>
    <string name="withdrawal_information">withdrawal information</string>
    <string name="check_balance">check balance</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="atmfinfo">Your debit or credit card is a powerful tool for spending.
        That little piece of plastic has everything you need to spend money overseas, in your hometown, and online. How does it work?
        Let"’"s look at each of the features on your card, starting with the front of your card.

    \n 1. Bank branding: this tells you which card you have. Your card might simply show the bank name, or it might display a logo.

    \n 2. Your card number is one of the most important things on the card. It is the 16 digit number that points to your account with the card issuer Bank
        and those are the digits you will need to provide when making purchases online or by phone.

    <b>Protect your card number:</b> be careful where you write it down, and limit who sees the number. When card numbers get stolen by fraudsters,
        they can be used to make purchases in your account. You might not have to pay for those purchases, but cleaning up the mess can be inconvenient.

    To shop online, you need more than just a card number. You willll also need the card"’"s expiration date and security code
        (often a three digit code on the back of the card, but this varies by issuer  read about the back of your card for details). Most systems also ask for your name.

    If you are using a debit card that"’"s linked to your checking account, your card number is different from your checking account number.
        This might be confusing because your checking account number is shown on your checks  but your card number is different.

    \n 3. Cardholders name: this is the person authorized to use the card. That person did"\\\\"nt necessarily open the account they might simply
        have permission to spend from the account. Only authorized card users can make purchases with a debit or credit card, and merchants are
        encouraged to ask for ID before accepting payment with a card.

    \n 4. Smart chips make cards more secure than traditional magnetic stripe only cards. They make it harder for thieves to use stolen credit card numbers.
        While common (and sometimes a necessity) overseas, banks in the United States have been slow to adopt smart cards. After 2015, banks will have more
        motivation to add these security features they face more risk of fraud with magnetic stripe transactions.

    If your card has a chip, use it whenever possible. The chip adds a single use code to the transaction, which makes stolen data much less useful.
        Preventing fraud can keep costs down for everybody, and it means you"’"re less likely to have to replace cards and update card numbers when your information gets stolen.
        Read more about how chip enabled cards work.


    \n 5. Expiration date: from time to time, youll need to replace your card. The move to smarter cards is just one reason banks issue new cards.
        Your expiration date is important because it"’"s required for purchases you make online or over the phone  you"’"ll need to provide the correct
        date for your transaction to be approved. Your bank will generally automatically mail you a new card when old cards expire.

    \n 6. Payment network logo: this tells you what type of card you have. Common examples include MasterCard, Visa, and Discover.
        If making purchases online, there might be a drop-down menu that requires you to select which network your card belongs to.
        These logos are also helpful when you plan to use your card to pay for goods or services  merchants often display stickers or placards
        that tell you which cards they accept (and you can of course ask which cards are accepted as well).
</string>
    -----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="atmbinfo">The back of a debit or credit card contains important features. There is more to making payments than reading off a card number.

   \n 1. Magnetic stripe: this black strip contains information about you and your card, which can be read by specialized devices known as card readers.
        Every time you swipe your card at a merchant, you are running the magnetic stripe through a card reader so that your card can be charged.
        Magnetic stripes provide your name, card number, expiration date, and other details. If that information is stolen (whether manually or by a card skimming device),
        it can be used to create a fake card  with a magnetic stripe that has the same information as your card.

    Magnetic stripes occasionally wear down, especially if you are a heavy card user, and they can be disturbed by strong magnets.
        If your stripe stops working, merchants may need to punch in your card number by hand (which they may be reluctant to do for several reasons),
        but you can order replacement cards with a new stripe.

   \n 2. Hologram: some cards display a hologram (or a mirror like section that shows a three dimensional image that seems to move as you change your viewing angle).
        Holograms are security features which help merchants identify valid cards they are not easy to fake. Sometimes holograms appear on the front of your card.

   \n 3. Bank contact information: if you need to get in touch with your bank, use the contact information on the back of your card.
        This is not only convenient  when you use that contact information you know that you"’"re really talking with somebody from your bank.
        This is especially important if you get a call or email that might be from your bank (but might also be from a fraudster).
        Instead of using the contact information provided in the call or email, call the number on the back of your card just to be safe.

    It"’"s a good idea to keep contact information from your bank stored separately from your card.
        If you lose your card, you"’"ll want to contact your bank as soon as possible.

   \n 4. Signature panel: your card must be signed before you can use it, so sign your name in this area
        (it"’"s not easy to fit a signature there, but do your best). This is a requirement from card issuers,
        and merchants should also verify that you"’"ve signed the card. Some people write “SEE ID” in this area
        (hoping that merchants will demand identification from anybody who tries to use the card), but this is technically against your card issuer"’"s rules
        plus merchants don"’"t always notice or honor the request.

   \n 5. Security codes: are used to ensure that you have a legitimate, original card.
        If you use your card number to make a purchase online or by phone, you’ll need to provide more than just the card number and expiration date from the front of your card.
        The security code on the back is an additional hurdle for hackers that may have stolen your card number from merchant systems or with the help of a skimmer.

    Security codes might be referred to as CVV, CVV2, CVC, CSC, CID, or similar. Most websites just ask for a “security code” and provide a small box for you to type the code into.
        On Visa, MasterCard, and Discover cards, the code is a three digit code on the back of your card.
        The preceding four digits (“3456” in the image above) are the last four digits of your card number.
        On American Express cards, the four digit code is on the front of the card  look above your card number on the right side of the card.

    Your security code, like all the other numbers on your card, is an important piece of information. Don"’"t share that code unless necessary.

   \n 6. Network logos: your card might have additional network logos on the back, often in the lower right corner.
        These logos can help you figure out which ATMs you can use for free. You can of course use other ATMs, but you"\\"ll
        most likely pay fees to the ATM operator, and you might pay additional fees to your bank or lender.
</string>
    --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="bominfo"><b>Bank of Maharashtra</b> is a major public sector bank in India. Government of India holds 81.61 percent of the total shares.
        The bank has 15 million customers across the length and breadth of the country served through 1895 branches as of 5 April 2016.
        It has largest network of branches by any public sector bank in the state of Maharashtra.
</string>
    <string name="bobinfo"><b>Bank of Baroda</b> is an Indian state owned banking and financial services company headquartered in Vadodara
        (earlier known as Baroda) in Gujarat India.It is the second largest bank in India next to State Bank Of India.
        Its headquarters is in Vadodara it has a corporate office in the Bandra Kurla Complex in Mumbai.
         Based on 2014 data it is ranked 801 on Forbes Global 2000 list.
        BoB has total assets in excess of
          3.58 trillion a network of 5326 branches in India and abroad and over 8000 ATMs.
</string>
    <string name="boiinfo"><b>Bank of India</b> (BoI) is commercial bank with headquarters in Mumbai Maharashtra India.
        Founded in 1906 it has been government-owned since nationalisation in 1969.
        However, some branches are individually owned such as Kandia  Indonesia etc.
        Bank of India has 4828 branches as on 31 December 2013, including 56 offices outside India
        which includes five subsidiaries five representative offices and one joint venture.[citation needed]
        BoI is a founder member of SWIFT (Society for Worldwide Inter Bank Financial Telecommunications)
        which facilitates provision of cost-effective financial processing and communication services.
</string>
    <string name="caninfo"><b>Canara Bank</b> is an Indian state owned bank headquartered in Bangalore Karnataka.
        It was established at Mangalore in 1906 making it one of the oldest banks in the country.
        The government nationalized the bank in 1969. As of September 2016, the bank had a network of 5860 branches
        and more than 10026 ATMs spread across India. The bank also has offices abroad in London, Hong Kong Moscow
        Shanghai Doha Bahrain South africa Dubai Tanzania and New York.
</string>
    <string name="cbinfo"><b>Central Bank of India</b> a government owned bank, is one of the oldest and largest commercial banks in India.
        It is based in Mumbai which is the financial capital of India and capital city of state of Maharashtra.
        The bank has 4741 branches 5000 ATMs and 4 extension counters across 27 Indian states and three Union Territories.
        At present Central Bank of India has overseas office at Nairobi Hong Kong and a joint venture with Bank of India
        Bank of Baroda and the Zambian government. The Zambian government holds 40 per cent stake and each of the banks has
        20 per cent. Recently it has also opened a representative office at Nairobi in Kenya.
</string>
    <string name="hdfcinfo"><b>HDFC Bank</b> (Housing Development Finance Corporation) is an Indian banking and financial services
        company headquartered in Mumbai, Maharashtra. It has about 87555 employees and has a presence in Bahrain
        Hong Kong and Dubai. HDFC Bank is the second largest private bank in India as measured by assets.
        It is the largest bank in India by market capitalization as of February 2016.
        It was ranked 69th in 2016 BrandZTM Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands.
    </string>
    <string name="icicinfo">
        <b>ICICI Bank</b> (Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation of India)
        is an Indian multinational banking and financial services company headquartered in Mumbai
        Maharashtra India, with its registered office in Vadodara. In 2014 it was the second largest
        bank in India in terms of assets and third in term of market capitalisation. It offers a wide range
        of banking products and financial services for corporate and retail customers through a variety of
        delivery channels and specialised subsidiaries in the areas of investment banking life non life
        insurance, venture capital and asset management.
        The bank has a network of 4450 branches and 13995 ATMs in India and has a presence in 19 countries including India
</string>
    <string name="sbinfo">
        <b>State Bank of India</b> (SBI) is an Indian multinational public sector banking and financial services company.
        It is a government owned corporation with its headquarters in Mumbai, Maharashtra.
        As of 2014 to 15 it had assets of 20.480 trillion (US$300 billion) and more than 14000 branches,
        including 191 foreign offices spread across 36 countries making it the largest banking and financial
        services company in India by assets. The company is ranked 232nd on the Fortune Global 500 list of the
        worlds biggest corporations as of 2016.The bank traces its ancestry to British India through the Imperial Bank of India
        to the founding in 1806 of the Bank of Calcutta making it the oldest commercial bank in the Indian Subcontinent.
        Bank of Madras merged into the other two presidency banks in British India Bank of Calcutta and Bank of Bombay
        to form the Imperial Bank of India which in turn became the State Bank of India in 1955. Government of India owned
        the Imperial Bank of India in 1955 with Reserve Bank of India (India s Central Bank) taking a 60 percent stake and renamed
        it the State Bank of India. In 2008 the government took over the stake held by the Reserve Bank of India.State Bank
        of India is a banking behemoth and has 20percent market share in deposits and loans among Indian commercial banks
</string>
    <string name="pnbinfo">
        <b>Punjab National Bank</b> is an Indian multinational banking and financial services company.
        It is a state owned corporation based in New Delhi India. Founded in 1894 the bank has over 6968 branches
        and over 9656 ATMs across 764 cities. It serves over 80 million customers
    </string>
    <string name="ubinfo"><b>Union Bank of India</b> (UBI) (BSE 532477) is one of the largest government-owned banks of India
        (the government owns 63.44 of its share capital). It is listed on the Forbes 2000 and has assets of USD 13.45
        billion. All the banks branches have been networked with its 6909 ATMs as on 30 September 2015. Its online
        Telebanking facility are available to all its Core Banking Customers individual as well as corporate.
        has representative offices in Abu Dhabi United Arab Emirates Beijing, Peoples Republic of China London and
        Shanghai and branches in Hong Kong Dubai Antwerp and Sydney.
        The bank had 4500 branches in India as of 31 March 2016
    </string>
    <string name="ucoinfo">
    <b>UCO Bank</b>, formerly United Commercial Bank, established in 1943 in Kolkata,
    is a major government-owned commercial bank of India. During FY 2013-14, its total business
    was ₹ 4.55 lakh crore. Based on 2014 data, it is ranked 1860 on Forbes Global 2000 List.
    UCO Bank was ranked 294th among India\s most trusted brands according to the Brand Trust Report 2014,
    a study conducted by Trust Research Advisory. It was a rise of 796 ranks considering it was listed
    at the 1090th position among India\s most trusted brands in the Brand trust Report 2013.
    As of 6 January 2013 the bank had 4,000 plus service units 49 zonal offices spread all over India.
    It also has two overseas branches, on each in Singapore and Hong Kong. UCO Bank\s headquarters is on BTM Sarani, Kolkata.
    </string>
    
    <string name="alinfo">
    <b>Allahabad Bank</b> is a nationalised bank with its headquarters in Kolkata, India.
    It is the oldest joint stock bank in India. On 24 April 2014, the bank entered 
    into its 150th year of establishment. It was founded in Allahabad in 1865.

As of 31 March 2012, Allahabad Bank had over 2,500 branches across India.
The bank did a total business of INR 3.1 trillion during the FY 2012-13.
 The bank has a branch in Hong Kong and a representative office in Shenzen.

The bank\s market capitalisation in May 2013 was US$1.28 billion and it ranked #1466 on the Forbes Global 2000 list.
    </string>
    <string name="andinfo" formatted="false">
        <b>Andhra Bank</b> (BSE: 532418) is a medium-sized public sector bank (PSB) of India, with a network of 2803 branches,
        4 extension counters, 38 satellite offices and 3636 automated teller machines (ATMs) as of 31 Mar 2016.
        During 2011–12, the bank entered the states of Tripura and Himachal Pradesh. The bank now operates in 25 states
        and three Union Territories. Andhra Bank has its headquarters in Hyderabad, India.

The Government of India owns 63.97% of its share capital as on 31 Dec 2015. The state owned Life Insurance Corporation of
 India holds 7.66% of the shares. The bank has done a total business of ₹3,106 billion (US$46 billion) and has earned a net
 profit of ₹5.40 billion (US$80 million) for the Financial Year 2015-16.

Andhra Bank is a pioneer in introducing Credit Cards in the country in 1981.
    </string>
 <string name="copinfo">
     <b>Corporation Bank</b> is a public sector banking company headquartered in Mangalore, India.
     The bank has pan-India presence with 8,000 functional units comprising 2200 branches,
     1800+ ATMs and 3,000 branchless banking units as of 30 January 2015.

The total business of the bank during the financial year 2014-15 has been ₹3,44,412 crore 
  (equivalent to ₹3.6 trillion or US$54 billion in 2016), as of 31 March 2015. The total deposits
     have grown to ₹1,99,346 crore (equivalent to ₹2.1 trillion or US$31 billion in 2016). 
     Total income of the bank reached ₹21,038.02 crore (equivalent to ₹220 billion or US$3.3 billion in 2016) during this period. 
     Operating profit of the bank reached ₹965.37 crore (equivalent to ₹10 billion or US$150 million in 2016) and net profit ₹584.26
     crore (equivalent to ₹617 crore or US$92 million in 2016).
 </string>
    <string name="dbinfo">
        <b>Dena Bank</b>, headquartered in Mumbai, is owned by the Government of India,
        and as per latest data the total branch network stands at 1,773 and plans 
        to open 404 new branches in FY 2015-16 The bank was founded in 1938 and the Indian government nationalized it in 1969.
    </string>
    <string name="ininfo">
        <b>Indian Bank</b> is an Indian state-owned financial services company established in 1907 and headquartered in Chennai, India.
        It has 20,661 employees, 2594 branches and is one of the top performing public sector banks in India.
        It has overseas branches in Colombo and Jaffna in Sri Lanka, and in Singapore, and 223 correspondent banks in 71 countries. 
        Since 1969 the Government of India has owned the bank.
    </string>
    <string name="iobinfo" formatted="false">
        <b>Indian Overseas Bank</b> (IOB) is a major public sector bank based in Chennai (Madras),
        with about 3700 domestic branches, including 1150 branches in Tamil Nadu, 3 extension counters,
        and eight branches and offices overseas as of 30 September 2014. Indian Overseas Bank has an ISO
        certified in-house Information Technology department, which has developed the software that its 
        branches use to provide online banking to customers; the bank has achieved 100% networking status
        as well as 100% CBS status for its branches. IOB also has a network of about 3300 ATMs all over India.
    </string>
    <string name="orbinfo">
        <b>Oriental Bank of Commerce</b> is an India-based bank established in Lahore
        (then the city of British India, and currently in Pakistan), is one of the public sector banks in India.
    </string>
    <string name="pnsinfo" formatted="false">
        <b>Punjab &amp; Sind Bank</b>  is a government-owned bank (79.62%), with headquarters in New Delhi.
        Of its 1466 branches spread throughout India, 623 branches are in Punjab state.
        Its net profit is Rs. 121.35 crores and net NPA is 3.55% for the year ending 2014-15.
        The bank\s operating profit for the year ending 2014-15 is Rs. 775.45 crores.
        Total business of the bank was Rs. 1,51,511 crores for the year ending 2014-15 and Business per employee is Rs. 15.95 crore. 
        The net worth of the bank as on 31.03.15 is Rs. 4812 crore.
    </string>
    <string name="syninfo">
        <b>Syndicate Bank</b> is one of the oldest and major commercial banks of India.
        It was founded by T M A Pai, Upendra Pai and Vaman Kudva. At the time of its establishment,
        the bank was known as Canara Industrial and Banking Syndicate Limited. The bank, along with
        13 major commercial banks of India, was nationalised on 19 July 1969, by the Government of India.
        The Bank is headquartered in Manipal, Karnataka, India
    </string>
    <string name="ubiinfo">
<b>United Bank of India</b> (UBI) is an Indian government-owned financial services company headquartered in Kolkata, West Bengal, India.
Presently the bank has a three-tier organisational setup consisting of its Head office in Kolkata, 35 Regional offices and 2005
branches spread all over India. However, its major presence is in eastern India. The bank has three full-fledged overseas branches,
one each at Kolkata, New Delhi and Mumbai. United Bank of India now aims to expand its international activities.

On 30 March 2009, the Indian government approved the restructuring of United Bank of India.
The government proposed to invest 2.5 billion rupees in shares by 31 March and another 5.50 billion
in the next fiscal year in Tier-I capital instruments. The move is part of the Indian government\s program
to improve the capital base of the state-owned banks.
    </string>
    <string name="vijinfo">
        <b>Vijaya Bank</b> is a fastest growing Public Sector Bank with its Corporate Office in Bangalore, Karnataka, India.
        It is one of the nationalised banks in India. The Bank offers a wide range of financial products and services
        to the customers through its various delivery channels. The Bank has a network of 1900 branches (August 2016)
        throughout the country and over 3500 customer touch points including 1651 ATMs.
    </string>
    <string name="step1">
Step 1 : Insert Card

<b>ATM cards comes in two types</b> — debit cards and credit cards. Debit cards are mostly used in ATMs,
and it offers you to withdrawal cash which you have in your savings account. Credit
card are generally used for shopping only but as a short term loan from the bank.

But in todays topic we will learn about the process of withdrawal money from ATM through your card.
Now first insert your ATM card in the ATM machine.(you may see a blinking green light in the machine,
 where you have to put your card.) please keep in mind to insert your card as the picture shows; otherwise the
 machine could not be able to read your card.
    </string>
    <string name="step2">Step 2 : Select your language
 This is the most easiest task to do I think. Select the language you like
    </string>
    <string name="step3">Step 3 : Enter your PIN
Now come the most important part. Use Keypad to enter your 4 digit pin.
Please make sure some things before you enter your pin
1. There is no camera or any person who can see your pin number​
\n2. Always make sure that the pin is entering by you is the same pin of that ATM card(otherwise the card could be locked after 3 wrong attempts)
</string>
    <string name="step4">Step 4 : Transaction Type
You can see now many types of options like Withdraw Money, Deposit Money, Balance Enquiry, Bill Pay etc. For withdrawal cash you have to chose Withdraw Money option.</string>
    <string name="step5">Step 5 : Account Type
ATM screen will show various types of account. Select your account type that may be saving or current etc.
</string>
    <string name="step6">Step 6 : Enter Amount
It is also a easy task. Chose the amount you want to withdrawal. But make sure that the amount you are entering is not more than your account balance.And press correct option.
</string>
    <string name="step7">Step 7 : Take Your Money
Now comes the most interesting part. The money comes from the cash dispenser slot in the machine. Take your money before 30 second.Then a question would appear on the and ask you would like to take a receipt. Press yes to proof that you withdrew money and check the balance.
</string>
    <string name="step8">Step 8: Another Transactions
If you want another transaction, chose that option.</string>
    <string name="step9">Step 9: Ending Your Session
Once you have completed your transaction press cross or cancel button before leave the machine room.Do not forget to take your card and money and all your belongings!
</string>

    <string name="about_your_atm_card">About Your ATM Card</string>

<string name="bcheck1">
   1. Get your ATM/debit card. Make sure you activate it and know your personal identification number (PIN) before going to the ATM.
    In some cases, it will activate the first time you place it in the ATM.
</string>
 <string name="bcheck2">
       2. Insert your ATM card into an ATM. You can avoid fees by using your bank"’"s ATM,
        but most machines will allow you to check your balance for free.
 </string>

<string name="bcheck3">
   3. Type in your PIN on the machine. Your “PIN” stands for personal identification number,
    a four-digit number you should have set up when you opened your account. Then,
    look for the menu that gives you options. Scroll through these options until you find one that includes the word “balance.”
</string>

<string name="bcheck4">
   4. Select the option to view your balance. Then, you will be able to go back and make a withdrawal or print that balance.
</string>

<string name="bcheck5">
   5. Opt to withdraw money from the ATM.
    Ask for a receipt. Your checking balance will be printed onto your receipt for your records.
</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3715652664770345/9286598713</string>
    <string name="Haw">How ATMs Work</string>
    <string name="hawinfo">Automated teller machine is an electronic telecommunications device that enables the customers cash withdrawal, without the need for a human cashier, clerk or bank teller.
In most modern cash machines, the customer is identified by inserting a plastic ATM card with a magnetic stripe or a plastic smart card with a chip that contains a unique card number.
        Authentication is provided by the customer entering a personal identification number (PIN).
A cash machine typically has following control for the customers:
\n\n1]  Display screen
\n\n2]  Eight buttons around the screen,
\n\n3]  PIN pad similar in layout to a button phone or calculator keypad),
\n\n4] Card slot for the inserting the card
\n\n5] Record printer (to provide the customer with a record of the transaction

</string>
    <string name="toc">Type Of Card</string>
    <string name="credit_card">Credit Card</string>
    <string name="debit_or_atm_card">Debit Or Atm Card</string>
    <string name="atm_card_only">Atm Card Only</string>
    <string name="card_payment_getway">Card Payment Getway</string>
    <string name="ci">When dealing with a bank you generally have \n two types of transactions.

  \n\n 1]  <b>Deposit</b> your money and then use it eventually when you need it.
        In this case the maximum amount you can spend is equal the balance in your account.
        In this case you are not charged back interest on the amount you spend as it is your own money.
        In this case you spend exactly as much as you need and nothing more

 \n \n 2] Second type is <b>borrow money</b>b> from the bank for your use and then pay it back in the either all at once or in agreed installments.
        In this case you are charged interest by the bank for the money that you use. So you end up spending more than you need.
    \n \n
        Important information
    \n \n
        ATM / Debit card Pin number - this is a four digit security number that is required to be used with the card for all the transactions. It is generally posted to the registered address of the customer in a secure post by the bank.
        Never share your Pin number with anyone or even with any bank person (employee). try and remember the Pin. <b>Do not</b> write the pin on the back of the card or any where
        because if the card is lost and has the pin with it any one can steal money from your bank account.
    </string>
    <string name="cci" formatted="false"><b>What is a credit card?</b>
        \n A credit card allows you to borrow money from your bank to make your purchases.
        As long as you pay back the money you borrowed within the “grace period” of 25-30 days, you don’t have to pay extra.
        If you don’t pay it back in that time period, you’ll have to pay interest — a percentage of the money you owe the bank — on top of what you borrowed. Credit cards generally have the highest interest compared to any other method of borrowing money from bank.
        On an average the interest annually is 24%
    </string>
    <string name="ac">\n \n <b>ATM card</b>

\nAn ATM card is a bank issued card that enables a customer to access an automated teller machine (ATM or ABM) in order to perform transactions such
        as deposits, cash withdrawals, obtaining account information, etc. ATM cards are known by a variety of names such as bank card, MAC (money access card), client card and cash card, among others.
        Most payment cards, such as debit and credit cards can also function as ATM cards, although ATM-only cards are also available.

 n\ \n <b>Interbank networks</b> allow the use of ATM cards at ATMs of banks and financial institutions other than those of
        the institution that issued the cards. There is a limit of number of free cash withdrawal transaction per month
        from other bank ATM which is usually 3 per month. After 3 withdrawal in a month from other bank the 4th withdrawal onwards
        in that month you will be charged.
    </string>
    <string name="dc">\n  \n  <b>What is a debit card?</b>

\n \n A debit card is a plastic payment card that can be used instead of cash when making purchases.
        You can use this card to buy groceries, pay hotel bill, pay electricity and telephone bill,
        pay for petrol and diesel. The money you spend with the card comes directly from the users bank account when performing
        a transaction. This means that you are not borrowing any money from the bank and hence they will not charge you any interest
        for that money. You are withdrawing and essentially spending money from your bank account using debit card.

\nDebit cards usually also allow for instant withdrawal of cash, acting as the  ATM card for withdrawing cash.
    </string>
    <string name="pg">\n  \n  <b>What is card Payment Gateway?</b>
        \n \n When you have to go from one city to another you have to use various roads and highway to reach your destination.
        For example Mumbai to Goa. If you are starting from Mumbai then it will be your source and Goa will be your destination.
        \nSimilarly when you make a payment for anything at a shop the money needs to go from your bank to the shop.
        This will need a digital road or network of digital roads. The Payment gateway makes and provides this network of roads.
        \nHence when you are buying things at any shop with your card it is better to confirm at the shop that
        they take you type of card\'s payment gateway since not all shops accept all the cards.
        \nVarious companies that provide this payment gateway for cards (digital network of roads) are-
        \n \n &#8226;Visa card
        \n &#8226;Master card
        \n &#8226;American express
        \n &#8226;Maestro
        \n \n Master and Visa cards are the most popular type of payment card methods covering 90% of the banks and shops.
    </string>
    <string name="wd">\n  \n <b>Borrow </b>– get a loan from the bank

\n \n <b>Transfer money</b> – send money from a bank account to another bank account. It can be within the same bank or different banks

\n \n <b>Deposit </b> – put some or part of you money into your account at the bank.

\n1] You can either deposit money by cash

\n2] You can use cheque to transfer money into your account

\n \n <b>Withdraw </b> – get part or all of your money from your account in the bank

\n1] This can be done at the bank with a passbook and slip over the counter

\n2] Or by a cheque at the bank over the counter

\n3] Or with a card at the ATM machine



\n  \n  <b>Interbank networks </b> – Network between banks over which all the banks can talk to each other for transactions
    </string>
    <string name="bank_related_word_definations">Bank related Word Definations</string>
    <string name="few_standard_error_message_of_atm_machine">Few standard Error message of ATM machine</string>
    <string name="select_your_bank">Select Your Bank</string>
    <string name="how_to_shop_with_your_debit_card_physicaly">How To shop with your debit card physically</string>
    <string name="how_to_shop_online">How To shop online</string>

    <string name="swc">While each brand of credit card machine is slightly different, most operate in the same way.


\n<b>Step 1</b>

\n A shop attendant will request for your card. give it to them but make sure they only use it to either swipe it in the sales machine or if your card has a chip they will
        insert it the bottom of the card reader.
\n<b>Step 2</b>

\n Typically , the operator will input the amount and then hand the machine to you to input the pin.
        Enter your pin with the keypad and observe that with every digit you press the screen shows a &#42; so after you enter the pin the screen should show &#42; &#42; &#42; &#42;.
        If you accidentally input the wrong amount, look for the "clear" or "delete" key and start over.
\n<b>Step 3</b>
Hand over the machine to the operator.
\nWait for the sale process to complete.
\n<b>Step 4</b>

\n After the sale is completed successfully the machine will print a receipt .
        The operator will request you to sign the receipt copy for the shop.
\n<b>Step 5</b>

\nTake your card and the receipt from the operator.
    </string>
    <string name="osinfo">Because of their low overhead, online retailers often offer lower prices than brick-and-mortar stores.
        Snag a deal on free shipping and your are almost guaranteed to save money by purchasing online. But before you get the
        goods you have got to pay for them, and one of the easiest, simplest, safest ways of doing so is paying with a credit card or debit card.
    </string>
    <string name="os1"><b>https&#58;&#47;&#47;</b> at the start of the web page address generally means the site is secure and encrypted.

   \n1] Some browsers use the symbol of a closed padlock to denote a secure network connection. You can also look for "[https" https"] in front of the Internet address,
        instead of the normal "[http," http ,"] to indicate a secure network.
   \n2] <b>Note Precautions you need to take</b>  Avoid using public wifi network for internet shopping and sending credit card information by e-mail over an unsecured network.
        Although e-mail might seem private, its all too easy for another user on the same network and to monitor your transmission.

</string>
    <string name="os2">Input the address of the website you intend to purchase from in your browsers address window.
      \n  Do your best to go directly to the site instead of searching for it or following a link; this minimizes your risk
        of ending up at a phishing site that mimics the original in order to gather your credit card information. Above all,
        do not follow links from e-mails to purchase items unless you are absolutely certain the e-mail did come from the legitimate
        merchant. These phishing, or mimic, e-mails are a very common scam.
    </string>
    <string name="os3">On a shopping site it works similar to a store or shop. You can choose multiple things and add them to your cart.
                "Add to Cart" on the item page next to the item.
    </string>
    <string name="os4">After adding all the desired items to the cart it is then time to <b>check out</b>. To do a check out
        Usually this entails looks for the icon of a shopping cart (or the word "Cart") and clicking the icon/word. Then click "Check Out" or "Check Out Now."
    </string>
    <string name="os5">Input your shipping information. You might not see your final price until youve done this,
        as the website needs your zip or postal code to calculate shipping charges.
    </string>
    <string name="os6">Input your billing information too. This should match the billing information for your credit card.
        \n Many websites give you an option to copy your shipping address into the billing address
        fields with the click of a single button.
    </string>
    <string name="os7">Input your credit card information. This includes:
        \n Your name as it appears on the credit card.
    \n The credit card number.
    \n The credit card expiration date.
    \n The 3- or 4- digit security code on the back of the credit card.
    \n You might also need to provide the billing zip code for the credit card again, or the telephone
        number listed on your credit card statement.
    </string>
    <string name="os8">Click the appropriate button to complete the credit card sale. </string>
    <string name="os9">Print the confirmation screen or proof of purchase you receive upon completing the transaction,
        and keep this in a safe place until the item you paid for arrives.
    </string>

    <string name="bob1">Dip your ATM card into the ATM machine.(you may see a blinking green light in the machine,
 where you have to put your card.) please keep in mind to insert your card as the picture shows; otherwise the
 machine could not be able to read your card.</string>
    <string name="bob2">Select your preferred language</string>
    <string name="bob3">Enter your four digit pin. Now come the most important part. Use Keypad to enter your 4 digit pin.
Please make sure some things before you enter your pin
1. There is no camera or any person who can see your pin number​
\n2. Always make sure that the pin is entering by you is the same pin of that ATM card(otherwise the card could be locked after 3 wrong attempts)
 </string>
    <string name="bob4">You can avail services like Fast cash, cash withdrawal, Fund transfer, Mini statement etc</string>
    <string name="bob5">To withdraw money, choose cash withdrawal option</string>
    <string name="bob6">Select account type from which the cash is to be withdrawn</string>
    <string name="bob7">Enter the amount</string>
    <string name="bob8">Press ‘Correct’ to confirm.</string>
    <string name="bob9">If the amount entered is incorrect, press the ‘Incorrect’ icon</string>
    <string name="bob10">Press ‘Yes’ if you want the ATM receipt of this transaction or ‘No’ to proceed.</string>
    <string name="bob11">If you press ‘Yes’ a printed receipt will come out of the slot and please collect your cash.</string>
    <string name="sbi2">Please Choose Banking For Cash Withdrawal</string>
    <string name="sbi3">This is a check at the SBI machine to ensure the Keypad is working properly.On Scree you are requested to type
    any two digit number between ten to ninety nine and press yes</string>
    <string name="sbi4">Select Current or Savings Account, normally most have savings account</string>
    <string name="mc">Not all the ATM machines are same. In fact there is a lot of difference between ATM machine due to changes in the technology over time. We will try and cover most of the common differences you may see around.</string>
    <string name="mc1">	 <b>Types Screen</b> - Touch and Non touch – This is a difference similar to old basic Nokia phones and now the android smart phones.
\n\n2)	<b>how Selection options from the screen</b></string>
        <string name="mc2">
<b>a) By Buttons</b>- Older machines have buttons next to the screen border and you can select the desired option by pressing the button next to it
            on the border either to the left or the right
</string>
    <string name="mc3">
        <b>b) By Screen</b> The newer machine have touch screen and you select the option you want by pressing it on the screen
</string>
    <string name="mc4">
<b>3) What is Keypad and its use</b> – As the image shows the keypad has zero to nine digits similar to a phone keypad and is used to enter ATM pin number
        and when withdrawing money it can be used to enter amount you want to withdraw.
        To make a correction in the amount you entered use the yellow correction key to erase the amount you had entered and put it in again.
        You can use red key any time to cancel everything that you are doing
        (and remove the card if the machine has a card intake slot which is explained below)
        \n\n <b>4) Card Slots and types</b>
</string>
    <string name="mc5">
	<b>a) Card Intake slot</b> – this is generally seen in older type of machine. Here when you insert the card in the machine,
        the machine will take the card inside the machine till you complete your transaction or cancel it and request the machine to exit.
        The card should be inserted as shown in the figure. generally with the image facing up, the numbers to the left side of the card’s center and the magnetic strip
        below to the right.
</string>
    <string name="mc6">
        <b> b) Card DIP slot</b> - Dipping card in the ATM machine slot is the act of sliding card in and pulling it out quickly through in that slot reader.
        The card should be inserted as shown in the figure. generally with the image facing up, the numbers to the left side of the card’s center and the magnetic strip
        below to the right. \nIf you dip the card too slowly or too fast you will get an error and will be requested to do try again.
</string>
    <string name="mc7">
        	<b>5) Money dispense slot</b>- As shown in the image. This is where the notes (money) are shared with you
        </string>
    <string name="mc8">
	<b>6) Printed slip slot</b> –you get a printed receipt of your transaction from this slot as shown in the image
</string>
    <string name="err"><b>Title:-no Cash</b></string>
    <string name="err1">When the ATM machine is out of money or very low with cash it automatically stops the process of allowing any new withdrawal.
        \n In that case the ATM screen will show Out of service or No Cash error </string>
    <string name="err2"><b>Title:- Out Of Service</b></string>
    <string name="err3">The ATM machine shuts down to avoid any further transaction issue and there could be multiple reasons for it.</string>
    <string name="err4"><b>Title:- Input smaller number</b></string>
    <string name="err5">The ATM machine may be low in cash or it is set to only dispense smaller amount. Generally each bank has a limit of how much you can
    withdraw from an ATM in a day \n \n Daily limit Generally = Rs 20000</string>
    <string name="err6"><b>Title:- Insufficient Fund error</b></string>
    <string name="err7">Your Bank account has less funds than the amount you are trying to withdraw. Please check your balance and try to
    withdraw the correct amount.</string>
</resources>