<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ATM Madat</string>
    <string name="lang_selection">Choose your language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="Marathi">मराठी</string>
    <string name="msg">Welcome All</string>
    <string name="nxt">Next</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="choose_your_bank">Choose Your Bank</string>
    <string name="back">previous</string>
    <string name="option_selc">Choose Your Option</string>
    <string name="bank_information">Bank information</string>
    <string name="atm_card_information">Atm card information</string>
    <string name="withdrawal_information">withdrawal information</string>
    <string name="check_balance">check balance</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="atmfinfo">Your debit or credit card is a powerful tool for spending.
        That little piece of plastic has everything you need to spend money overseas, in your hometown, and online. How does it work?
        Let"’"s look at each of the features on your card, starting with the front of your card.

    \n 1. Bank branding: this tells you which card you have. Your card might simply show the bank name, or it might display a logo for
        a specific program (such as a rewards program that your bank offers).

    \n 2. Your card number is one of the most important things on the card. It is the 16 digit number that points to your account with the card issuer,
        and those are the digits you"’"ll need to provide when making purchases online or by phone. If you use American Express, the card number is only 15 digits.

    Protect your card number: be careful where you write it down, and limit who sees the number. When card numbers get stolen by fraudsters,
        they can be used to make purchases in your account. You might not have to pay for those purchases, but cleaning up the mess can be inconvenient.

    To shop online, you need more than just a card number. You"’"ll also need the card"’"s expiration date and security code
        (often a three digit code on the back of the card, but this varies by issuer  read about the back of your card for details). Most systems also ask for your name.

    If you"’"re using a debit card that"’"s linked to your checking account, your card number is different from your checking account number.
        This might be confusing because your checking account number is shown on your checks  but your card number is different.

    \n 3. Cardholders name: this is the person authorized to use the card. That person did"'"nt necessarily open the account they might simply
        have permission to spend from the account. Only authorized card users can make purchases with a debit or credit card, and merchants are
        encouraged to ask for ID before accepting payment with a card.

    \n 4. Smart chips make cards more secure than traditional magnetic stripe only cards. They make it harder for thieves to use stolen credit card numbers.
        While common (and sometimes a necessity) overseas, banks in the United States have been slow to adopt smart cards. After 2015, banks will have more
        motivation to add these security features they face more risk of fraud with magnetic stripe transactions.

    If your card has a chip, use it whenever possible. The chip adds a single use code to the transaction, which makes stolen data much less useful.
        Preventing fraud can keep costs down for everybody, and it means you"’"re less likely to have to replace cards and update card numbers when your information gets stolen.
        Read more about how chip enabled cards work.


    \n 5. Expiration date: from time to time, youll need to replace your card. The move to smarter cards is just one reason banks issue new cards.
        Your expiration date is important because it"’"s required for purchases you make online or over the phone  you"’"ll need to provide the correct
        date for your transaction to be approved. Your bank will generally automatically mail you a new card when old cards expire.

    \n 6. Payment network logo: this tells you what type of card you have. Common examples include MasterCard, Visa, and Discover.
        If making purchases online, there might be a drop-down menu that requires you to select which network your card belongs to.
        These logos are also helpful when you plan to use your card to pay for goods or services  merchants often display stickers or placards
        that tell you which cards they accept (and you can of course ask which cards are accepted as well).
</string>
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="atmbinfo">The back of a debit or credit card contains important features. There is more to making payments than reading off a card number.

   \n 1. Magnetic stripe: this black strip contains information about you and your card, which can be read by specialized devices known as card readers.
        Every time you swipe your card at a merchant, you are running the magnetic stripe through a card reader so that your card can be charged.
        Magnetic stripes provide your name, card number, expiration date, and other details. If that information is stolen (whether manually or by a card skimming device),
        it can be used to create a fake card  with a magnetic stripe that has the same information as your card.

    Magnetic stripes occasionally wear down, especially if you are a heavy card user, and they can be disturbed by strong magnets.
        If your stripe stops working, merchants may need to punch in your card number by hand (which they may be reluctant to do for several reasons),
        but you can order replacement cards with a new stripe.

   \n 2. Hologram: some cards display a hologram (or a mirror like section that shows a three dimensional image that seems to move as you change your viewing angle).
        Holograms are security features which help merchants identify valid cards they are not easy to fake. Sometimes holograms appear on the front of your card.

   \n 3. Bank contact information: if you need to get in touch with your bank, use the contact information on the back of your card.
        This is not only convenient  when you use that contact information you know that you"’"re really talking with somebody from your bank.
        This is especially important if you get a call or email that might be from your bank (but might also be from a fraudster).
        Instead of using the contact information provided in the call or email, call the number on the back of your card just to be safe.

    It"’"s a good idea to keep contact information from your bank stored separately from your card.
        If you lose your card, you"’"ll want to contact your bank as soon as possible.

   \n 4. Signature panel: your card must be signed before you can use it, so sign your name in this area
        (it"’"s not easy to fit a signature there, but do your best). This is a requirement from card issuers,
        and merchants should also verify that you"’"ve signed the card. Some people write “SEE ID” in this area
        (hoping that merchants will demand identification from anybody who tries to use the card), but this is technically against your card issuer"’"s rules
        plus merchants don"’"t always notice or honor the request.

   \n 5. Security codes: are used to ensure that you have a legitimate, original card.
        If you use your card number to make a purchase online or by phone, you’ll need to provide more than just the card number and expiration date from the front of your card.
        The security code on the back is an additional hurdle for hackers that may have stolen your card number from merchant systems or with the help of a skimmer.

    Security codes might be referred to as CVV, CVV2, CVC, CSC, CID, or similar. Most websites just ask for a “security code” and provide a small box for you to type the code into.
        On Visa, MasterCard, and Discover cards, the code is a three digit code on the back of your card.
        The preceding four digits (“3456” in the image above) are the last four digits of your card number.
        On American Express cards, the four digit code is on the front of the card  look above your card number on the right side of the card.

    Your security code, like all the other numbers on your card, is an important piece of information. Don"’"t share that code unless necessary.

   \n 6. Network logos: your card might have additional network logos on the back, often in the lower right corner.
        These logos can help you figure out which ATMs you can use for free. You can of course use other ATMs, but you"'"ll
        most likely pay fees to the ATM operator, and you might pay additional fees to your bank or lender.
</string>
    --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string name="bominfo">Bank of Maharashtra is a major public sector bank in India. Government of India holds 81.61 percent of the total shares.
        The bank has 15 million customers across the length and breadth of the country served through 1895 branches as of 5 April 2016.
        It has largest network of branches by any public sector bank in the state of Maharashtra.
</string>
    <string name="bobinfo">Bank of Baroda is an Indian state owned banking and financial services company headquartered in Vadodara
        (earlier known as Baroda) in Gujarat India.It is the second largest bank in India next to State Bank Of India.
        Its headquarters is in Vadodara it has a corporate office in the Bandra Kurla Complex in Mumbai.
         Based on 2014 data it is ranked 801 on Forbes Global 2000 list.
        BoB has total assets in excess of
          3.58 trillion a network of 5326 branches in India and abroad and over 8000 ATMs.
</string>
    <string name="boiinfo">Bank of India (BoI) is commercial bank with headquarters in Mumbai Maharashtra India.
        Founded in 1906 it has been government-owned since nationalisation in 1969.
        However, some branches are individually owned such as Kandia  Indonesia etc.
        Bank of India has 4828 branches as on 31 December 2013, including 56 offices outside India
        which includes five subsidiaries five representative offices and one joint venture.[citation needed]
        BoI is a founder member of SWIFT (Society for Worldwide Inter Bank Financial Telecommunications)
        which facilitates provision of cost-effective financial processing and communication services.
</string>
    <string name="caninfo">Canara Bank is an Indian state owned bank headquartered in Bangalore Karnataka.
        It was established at Mangalore in 1906 making it one of the oldest banks in the country.
        The government nationalized the bank in 1969. As of September 2016, the bank had a network of 5860 branches
        and more than 10026 ATMs spread across India. The bank also has offices abroad in London, Hong Kong Moscow
        Shanghai Doha Bahrain South africa Dubai Tanzania and New York.
</string>
    <string name="cbinfo">Central Bank of India a government owned bank, is one of the oldest and largest commercial banks in India.
        It is based in Mumbai which is the financial capital of India and capital city of state of Maharashtra.
        The bank has 4741 branches 5000 ATMs and 4 extension counters across 27 Indian states and three Union Territories.
        At present Central Bank of India has overseas office at Nairobi Hong Kong and a joint venture with Bank of India
        Bank of Baroda and the Zambian government. The Zambian government holds 40 per cent stake and each of the banks has
        20 per cent. Recently it has also opened a representative office at Nairobi in Kenya.
</string>
    <string name="hdfcinfo">HDFC Bank (Housing Development Finance Corporation) is an Indian banking and financial services
        company headquartered in Mumbai, Maharashtra. It has about 87555 employees and has a presence in Bahrain
        Hong Kong and Dubai. HDFC Bank is the second largest private bank in India as measured by assets.
        It is the largest bank in India by market capitalization as of February 2016.
        It was ranked 69th in 2016 BrandZTM Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands.
    </string>
    <string name="icicinfo">
        ICICI Bank (Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation of India)
        is an Indian multinational banking and financial services company headquartered in Mumbai
        Maharashtra India, with its registered office in Vadodara. In 2014 it was the second largest
        bank in India in terms of assets and third in term of market capitalisation. It offers a wide range
        of banking products and financial services for corporate and retail customers through a variety of
        delivery channels and specialised subsidiaries in the areas of investment banking life non life
        insurance, venture capital and asset management.
        The bank has a network of 4450 branches and 13995 ATMs in India and has a presence in 19 countries including India
</string>
    <string name="sbinfo">
        State Bank of India (SBI) is an Indian multinational public sector banking and financial services company.
        It is a government owned corporation with its headquarters in Mumbai, Maharashtra.
        As of 2014 to 15 it had assets of 20.480 trillion (US$300 billion) and more than 14000 branches,
        including 191 foreign offices spread across 36 countries making it the largest banking and financial
        services company in India by assets. The company is ranked 232nd on the Fortune Global 500 list of the
        worlds biggest corporations as of 2016.The bank traces its ancestry to British India through the Imperial Bank of India
        to the founding in 1806 of the Bank of Calcutta making it the oldest commercial bank in the Indian Subcontinent.
        Bank of Madras merged into the other two presidency banks in British India Bank of Calcutta and Bank of Bombay
        to form the Imperial Bank of India which in turn became the State Bank of India in 1955. Government of India owned
        the Imperial Bank of India in 1955 with Reserve Bank of India (India s Central Bank) taking a 60 percent stake and renamed
        it the State Bank of India. In 2008 the government took over the stake held by the Reserve Bank of India.State Bank
        of India is a banking behemoth and has 20percent market share in deposits and loans among Indian commercial banks
</string>
    <string name="pnbinfo">
        Punjab National Bank is an Indian multinational banking and financial services company.
        It is a state owned corporation based in New Delhi India. Founded in 1894 the bank has over 6968 branches
        and over 9656 ATMs across 764 cities. It serves over 80 million customers
    </string>
    <string name="ubinfo">Union Bank of India (UBI) (BSE 532477) is one of the largest government-owned banks of India
        (the government owns 63.44 of its share capital). It is listed on the Forbes 2000 and has assets of USD 13.45
        billion. All the banks branches have been networked with its 6909 ATMs as on 30 September 2015. Its online
        Telebanking facility are available to all its Core Banking Customers individual as well as corporate.
        has representative offices in Abu Dhabi United Arab Emirates Beijing, Peoples Republic of China London and
        Shanghai and branches in Hong Kong Dubai Antwerp and Sydney.
        The bank had 4500 branches in India as of 31 March 2016</string>
    <string name="step1">Step 1 : Insert Card
Insert Card

ATM cards comes in two types — debit cards and credit cards. Debit cards are mostly used in ATMs, and it offers you to withdrawal cash which you have in your savings account. Vise versa from credit card you could credit money from your account.

But in todays topic we will discourse about the process of withdrawal money from ATM through your card.
Now first insert your ATM card in the ATM machine.(you may see a blinking green light in the machine, where you have to put your card.) please mind to insert your card as the picture shows; otherwise the machine could not be able to read your card.</string>
    <string name="step2">Step 2 : Select your language
 This is the most easiest task to do I think. Select the language you like</string>
    <string name="step3">Step 3 : Enter your PIN
Now come the most important part. Use Keypad to enter your 4 digit pin.
Please make sure some things before you enter your pin
1. There is no camera or any person who can see your pin number​
2. Always make sure that the pin is entering by you is the same pin of that ATM card(otherwise the card could be locked)
</string>
    <string name="step4">Step 4 : Transaction Type
You can see now many types of options like Withdraw Money, Deposit Money, Balance Enquiry, Bill Pay etc. For withdrawal cash you have to chose Withdraw Money option.</string>
    <string name="step5">Step 5 : Account Type
ATM screen will show various types of account. Select your account type that may be saving or current etc.
</string>
    <string name="step6">Step 6 : Enter Amount
It is also a easy task. Chose the amount you want to withdrawal. But make sure that the amount you are entering is not more than your main balance.And press correct option.
</string>
    <string name="step7">Step 7 : Take Your Money
Now comes the most interesting part. The money comes from the cash dispenser machine. Take your money before 30 second.Then a question would appear on the and ask you would like to take a receipt. Press yes to proof that you withdrew money and check the balance.
</string>
    <string name="step8">Step 8: Another Transactions
If you want another transaction, chose that option.</string>
    <string name="step9">Step 9: Ending Your Session
Once you have completed your transaction press cross or cancel button before leave the machine room.Don not forget to take your card and money!
</string>

    <string name="about_your_atm_card">About Your ATM Card</string>
</resources>